Guide to the William Allen White Letters, 1889-1945
Department of Special Collections
William Allen White Letters,
1889-1945
Special Collections M0094
White, William Allen, 1868-1944.
.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Miss Helen Sutliff, 1946.
Biography
William Allen White was a journalist.
Scope and Content
Letters from White to Helen Sutliff, both of whom were members of the Class of 1890 at the University of Kansas. Includes letters from Sallie Lindsay White and William Lindsay White and a class song written by William Allen White in 1889.
Access Terms
Sutliff, Helen.; White, Sallie Lindsay.; White, William Allen.; White, William Lindsay.
Container List
- White, William A. Song / by Will A. White, Class of '90, 1889
  Song sung by the Junior Class at the reception given them by the Seniors, June 5, 1889.
- White, William A. Letter: copy, 1891 Jan. 21 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1910 June 10 to Jennie
- White, William A. Letter, 1911 Mar. 20 to Mrs. Wheeler
- White, William A. Letter, 1912 Nov. 13 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1913 Nov. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1914 Feb. 16 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1914 Apr. 25 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1914 Dec. 22 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1915 Feb. 12 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1915 Mar. 27 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1915 Mar. 27 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1915 Oct. 12 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1915 Dec. 4 to Effie Franklin
- White, William A. Letter, 1916 Sept. 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1917 Feb. 26 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1917 July 6 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1917 July 6 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1917 July 6 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1917 Aug. 11 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1917 Sept. 14 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1917 Sept. 25 to "Dear Girls"
- White, William A. Letter, 1918 Oct. to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1918 Nov. 6 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1918 Nov. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1918 Dec. 14 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 May 29 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 June 20 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 June 21 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 July 24 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 Sept. 2 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 Oct. 31 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 Nov. 3 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1919 Nov. 11 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 Jan. 12 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 Feb. 5 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 Feb. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 June 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 July 8 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 Aug. 25 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 Sept. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 Sept. 25 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1920 Dec. 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1921 Jan. 25 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1921 Jan. 25 to Jennie Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1921 Feb. 3 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1921 Mar. 26 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1921 June 7 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1921 July 21 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1921 Oct. 26 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 Mar. 25 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 June 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 June 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 June 20 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 July 3 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 Aug. 4 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 Aug. 7 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 Aug. 17 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Telegram, 1922 Sept. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 Nov. 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 Dec. 4 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1922 Dec. 22 to Helen Sutliff. Note: missing
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 Jan. 24 to Helen Sutliff
- Garves, Ruth Jane. Letter, 1923 Mar. 7 to Helen Sutliff
- Garves, Ruth Jane. Letter, 1923 Apr. 4 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 June 5 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 June 28 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 Sept. 7 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 Sept. 18 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 Oct. 3 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 Nov. 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1923 Dec. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1924 Feb. 16 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1924 Mar. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1924 Apr. 25 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1924 July 23 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1924 Aug. 14 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1924 Sept. 20 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1924 Oct. 4 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1924 Nov. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 Jan. 26 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 Mar. 9 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 June 6 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 June 16 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 June 24 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 Oct. 31 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 Dec. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1925 Dec. 18 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 Jan. 1 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 Feb. 27 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 Mar. 6 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 Mar. 25 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 Apr. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 Apr. 28 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 June 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 June 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1926 July 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1927 Feb. 19 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1927 Apr. 28 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1927 Dec. 2 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1927 Dec. 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1928 May 18 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1928 July 24 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1928 Oct. 4 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1928 Oct. 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1928 Nov. 15 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1929 Apr. 17 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1929 July 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1930 Feb. 21 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1930 May 27 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1931 Apr. 7 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1931 Dec. 23 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1932 Apr. 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1933 Feb. 4 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1933 May 16 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1933 Oct. 23 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1933 Dec. 5 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1934 May 23 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1934 July 11 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1934 Aug. 14 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1934 Nov. 9 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1934 Nov. 24 to Helen Sutliff
- Snow, Edith A. Letter: photocopy, to William A. White
- White, William A. Letter, 1935 Aug. 13 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1935 Oct. 11 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1935 Dec. 14 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1935 Dec. 16 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1936 Feb. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1936 June 3 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1936 Aug. 5 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1936 Dec. 23 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1937 Jan. 23 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Telegram, 1937 Feb. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1937 Apr. 5 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1937 May 20 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1937 Sept. 8 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1937 Sept. 22 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1937 Nov. 27 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1937 Dec. 6 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1938 Aug. 9 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1938 Aug. 12 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1938 Aug. 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1938 Oct. 11 to Helen Sutliff
- Ed. Letter, 1938 Oct. 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1938 Dec. 8 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1939 Mar. 18 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1939 Aug. 5 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1939 Nov. 1 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1939 Nov. 23 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1940 July 13 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1940 Oct. 17 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1941 Jan. 20 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1941 May 24 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1941 Aug. 29 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1941 Dec. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1942 Feb. 14 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1942 June 13 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1942 June 27 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1942 Dec. 16 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1943 Feb. 4 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1943 Feb. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1943 Apr. 2 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1943 June 11 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1943 Sept. 7 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1943 Sept. 30 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William A. Letter, 1943 Oct. 20 to Helen Sutliff
- Yearout, Minnie. Letter, 1943 Dec. 13 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1944 Jan. 18 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1944 Mar. 10 to Helen Sutliff
- Johnson, Walter. Letter, 1944 Aug. 12 to Helen Sutliff
- White, William L. Letter, 1944 Nov. 18 to Helen Sutliff
- White, Sallie. Letter, 1945 Jan. 11 to Helen Sutliff